Don't let impulse
(Heart's Answer)
decide the fate of a relationship.
My gosh.
Don't be impulsive.
Interpret it.
I mean
you're the interpretation master.
I trust you.
I think this
isn't easy to interpret.
I'd get in trouble.
Not easy to interpret.
But I hope you find happiness, Yu Yang.
I will.
Some people come into our lives
(Heart's Answer)
to teach us stuff.
Quite negative.
Read another one.
What if it's a good thing?
Oh no.
No.
When you're in a relationship,
you're constantly learning too.
Yeah.
It could be a good thing.
They teach you something.
It doesn't say whether it's good or bad.
It could be something good.
Yeah. I think that's very positive.
Want to go another round?
No need.
It's enough.
That will do.
Will I sleep well tonight?
(Look)
(Cui Kaiyi asks:
Will I sleep well tonight?)
Be an outsider once in a while.
(Heart's Answer)
Don't let prejudice cloud your judgment.
What even is this?
So I have prejudices against sleep?
Fine.
Who hasn't tried it yet?
You both.
You two.
(Haven't tried)
I tried it once,
but I can go again.
I have more aura now.
Yeah.
Don't pass it to me.
I'll grab it myself,
okay?
(Turns back)
Kidding.
(Hides)
Let me see.
Well...
Quick. Interpret it.
What is it?
You need to keep trying
(Heart's Answer)
to find someone suitable.
I suggest you
to read it backwards.
Let me.
What does it mean?
I'm a professional.
I'll interpret it.
Find someone suitable
and keep on trying.
Actually,
don't confuse cause and effect.
You need to keep trying
to find the right person.
That's it.
So I just need
to know them better.
You need
to put yourself out there
to find the right person.
That's why you're the pro.
So professional.
Yeah.
Seriously. With your skills.
I think you could make it a side hustle.
What should we talk about?
Is there anyone you girls
are leaning toward?
Your questions are so direct.
Can we ask that?
Ask something else.
What I meant earlier was...
I was saying
I don't really like that type.
Yeah. You don't like direct guys.
Those who are too direct.
I always thought girls liked guys
who don't pay them much attention.
You like guys who ignore you?
I like that.
You like to conquer them?
Yeah, I do.
So you like chasing guys?
I love it.
Love it?
Is there anyone you want to pursue now?
I think I need to get
to know them first.
I couldn't tell.
Yeah.
Remember I said
I'll open up slowly?
You'll understand me soon.
So exciting.
Are you the passive type?
I...
Depends on the guy.
If I like him,
and he's proactive,
I'll be a little more passive.
If he's passive,
I'll take more initiative.
I'm more on the passive side.
So I haven't been speaking up much.
I was worried people might think
I'm a little weird.
Not at all.
It's fine.
Wu Siying, you don't need
to do anything.
Just stand there and look pretty.
Plenty of people will like you.
You could stand there
without saying a word.
Just be yourself.
Those who like your type
will really like you.
Alright.
Thank you, everyone.
As for me,
I can't get to your level now.
(Laughs)
I really envy you.
I'm envious.
How hungry is everyone?
(Midnight snack time)
Anything edible.
Let's just make three packs of noodles,
and we will
add lots of vegetables.
A big pot of vegetables.
Sure.
We'll make a pot of vegetable soup.
Something like that.
Sounds good.
I think everyone's trying
to lose weight.
Let's just do two packs.
Sorry for the trouble.
Very healthy.
I'll use the most complicated method
to make the simplest dish.
I'll use the small pot then.
That's amazing.
(Praises)
I'll move for better viewing.
(Moves)
Now you can watch.
Really. Look.
(Laughs)
Everyone is
putting so much pressure on me.
No.
I think a man who can cook
is really attractive.
I'm about to cut my finger.
Then be careful.
The funny thing is
after all that buildup,
I ended up making
a pot of instant noodles.
(Bursts into laughter)
This is so funny.
I can already smell it.
Smells delicious.
Do you all want the soup?
Anyone who doesn't want it?
Me.
I'll take some for you without the soup.
Okay. Thank you.
This is without soup.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I'm gonna eat first.
Very light.
Not fattening at all.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
This is the best meal
I've eaten this whole week.
Is it really delicious?
Super delicious.
Treat yourself better next week.
Alright?
Okay. I'll wash the dishes.
(Follows)
It's fine. Just leave it there.
Leave it here.
Do I just pour it here?
Yeah, and leave the bowl here.
(Offers to help)
It's fine. We'll wash them.
You can leave.
No. I'll do it.
You really don't need to.
Just leave.
Four people washing a bowl.
We don't need to do this.
Those not washing
are just watching from the side.
Giving emotional support.
I can't even.
Can you stop washing?
Leave some for us.
This is perfect.
Here.
It's half of the dishes.
This will do.
We're lining up here.
No.
No way.
No one can touch my chopsticks.
See how tightly I'm holding it?
It's a dead grip.
Let's see. What's the procedure now?
This is great.
Hurry up.
Don't waste water.
No.
He took my chopsticks.
(A new day)
How about you all
help me get some practice?
A group photo.
Look here.
Let us...
I'll photoshop myself
inside later.
Okay.
Ready.
One,
two,
three.
Got it.
Great.
Perfect.
I think this one
will turn out well.
The rest...
How many are there?
This is nice too.
They're all pretty good.
This one.
(Crouches)
Take a look.
Can you zoom in?
Yeah.
Can this zoom in?
We got quite a few pictures.
So professional.
They really look great.
Yeah.
Like a family.
All of us.
Yes.
Mine
can take selfies.
Let me.
You have a great eye for beauty.
We can take selfies.
This way
we can see everyone.
(Turns around)
This is good.
Yes.
So I'll...
stand in front by myself?
(Asks)
Let's have
the most handsome guy hold it.
Whoever has the smallest face.
Yes.
The one with the smallest face.
(Points)
Zhao Xilun, you do it.
To be honest,
your face is smaller than mine.
I can't.
(Hands it over)
Come on.
Press this.
Here.
Okay.
The black one.
Then I'll
stand here.
Over here.
Let's see if I can
fit everyone in the frame.
Guys, why don't you
stand there.
We'll
move a little closer here.
(Moves)
Here we go.
Okay.
Three,
two,
one.
Alright.
Take a look.
(Hands it back)
Thank you.
I don't think I did a good job.
Take a look.
The one with a flash
is better.
(Praise)
So pretty.
How is it?
Every photo looks good.
Yes.
I brought a polaroid camera.
(Looks)
Let's take a polaroid photo.
Sure.
Take a few shots.
I'll go get it.
(Stands up)
For polaroids,
we can find better lighting.
Yes. Somewhere with better light.
That type of direct...
Uh, direct light.
Yeah.
Wait for me.
Okay.
(Grabs her polaroid camera)
Why don't the guys
help the girls
take photos?
How about that?
We'll use two cameras.
The girls
get VIP treatment.
Two cameras.
Here.
Both of us then.
Maybe think about
the setup first?
Setting. Composition.
This spot already looks good.
Facing away from this.
Stand here.
Inside here.
Right?
It works too.
Well.
This composition is great.
We'll do it here then.
Right?
Yeah.
Decide the composition.
What about standing here?
Here.
Just
like this.
So,
which position?
(Thinking)
Leave
the center spot for Sun Qimeng.
Let's just try.
Stand together when Sun Qimeng's back.
Just testing.
(Turns around)
Quick, Meng.
Only you left.
Only you're missing.
You can hold the camera
as a prop.
Then I will
take a picture of you girls.
Okay.
You girls
can scatter out.
It's not
that serious.
I'll take one first
for you to see.
Yeah. Let's just try it out.
Here.
Three,
two,
one.
See if you like
this composition.
(Taking a snapshot)
I think...
I think
you guys can stand closer
over here.
Move in front a little.
Your face will still look small.
Okay.
We can
take a few more pictures.
Just scatter around.
Then we'll...
Okay.
Sure.
Cool.
Whatever you say.
What do we do?
He got a picture here.
I think.
Is that so?
There's even a candid shot?
Yeah.
A candid shot.
We got two cameras.
This looks really nice.
(Praises)
Really pretty.
This tone is really nice.
Why don't we sit there
for a picture?
Sure.
Of course.
Okay.
Alright.
Three,
two,
one.
I think they're all nice.
For real.
Take a look.
Of course.
See for yourself.
So pretty.
It's beautiful.
Everyone looks great.
So good at taking photos.
(Praises)
So nice.
So amazing.
He's so skilled.
I'll reward you
with an individual polaroid.
Really?
Yes.
Hang on.
I need to freshen up.
(Laughs)
Freshen up.
I'm back.
Amazing.
Do you want to take it here?
Sure.
You can...
There's people behind you though.
You can
include them too.
Include them.
Perfect.
Sure.
Use them as the background
(Joking)
to make you stand out.
No!
You want a photo with them?
Yeah.
A group photo.
Candid shot.
I...
I'll give it a try.
This is my first time
taking a polaroid photo.
I've never used
this camera.
It'll be great.
Give it a shot.
Three,
two,
one.
So excited.
Can I...
can I
hide it first?
By all means.
Check it
when you get back.
He hid it.
(Looks over)
You'll destroy it if it's ugly, huh?
Destroy it if it's ugly.
Ugly.
If it's nice...
Let me think.
I'll stick it
on the front door.
On the fridge.
(Laughs)
Keep the mosquitoes away.
(Looks)
Shall we
go for a walk?
Sure.
Let's go.
(Looks back)
Have you seen the menu?
Not yet. I want to.
There's a menu there.
Is there anything you like?
I like something spicy.
So you like spicy food, Si.
(Menu)
What's Summer Breeze?
Grilled chicken sukiyaki.
I want this.
What do you want?
Let's hear everyone's
favorite dish.
Make a note.
This one's good.
(Sirloin steak)
What's this?
Steak.
Yes.
Cantonese cuisine.
Japanese cuisine.
This is...
Sichuan cuisine.
Hot pot.
Western food.
I noticed something.
Anything with meat
like foie gras
and raw meat,
you like all of them.
Could it be possible
that the candlelight is just beautiful?
It probably has...
You're like this.
You're choosing based on the names.
Shrimp is good too.
Garlic shrimp.
Napoleon foie gras.
That sounds delicious.
I think we can make it ourselves.
Right, let's learn to make
something from this menu every day.
One dish per person, okay?
I'll pick one.
A claiming session.
Udon noodles.
(Looks)
(Laughs)
Take a photo of the house.
I'll take one for you.
(Signal House)
Hang on. My mouth.
My mouth's open.
Take one of us guys.
All of us.
Sure.
Okay.
Take one
in front of the big house.
Come on.
Three,
two,
one.
Nice.
Look.
Let's go over there.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's check out
the riverside.
They even
have a swing.
There's a swing.
Yeah.
A single swing.
Are polaroids better taken at night
or during the day?
The one just now
was the first piece of film.
I've never used that camera before.
The one we just used?
Yes.
Who wants to go?
I think this scenery
suits you.
Okay.
Mind your skirt.
So beautiful.
She looks amazing
even with my naked eyes.
Take it from here.
She looks so natural.
So beautiful.
I want to capture
a first POV shot.
You can bend one leg slightly.
One leg.
Yes.
"Campus"
(Everyone praising)
"belle"!
(Turns around to look)
Such long legs.
Three,
two,
one.
Who is this beautiful girl?
This angle
looks super good.
Very pretty.
Adjust your dress.
That cold expression is gorgeous.
Yeah.
She's so stunning.
Cold expression.
(Breaks character instantly)
Take a look.
So pretty.
Beautiful.
Alright.
Come on, Sun Qimeng.
Careful.
Hold it steady.
Three,
two,
one.
So beautiful.
(Looks back)
Careful.
Her dress is amazing.
That dress of hers.
It even matches
the color of the swing.
Her smile is so pretty.
Yeah.
So good.
Perfect shot.
So beautiful.
So pretty.
New kid.
What do you mean?
You called me
new kid so many times today.
Come on.
I will let you take a photo
of me.
Alright, new kid.
(Checking out)
New kid, do you want to stand on it?
If you want me
to fall into the lake,
just say so.
Don't need to tell me
to stand on it.
Starting
with the tactics now.
"Stand"tics.
Making me stand on it.
Come on.
So beautiful.
Smile, new kid.
So cute.
Pretty.
So good at posing.
Three,
two,
one.
(Gradually closing in)
Getting closer and closer.
So pretty.
Taking turns.
Yeah.
Taking rounds.
A must-visit attraction here.
You taking photos?
Yeah.
Looks nice.
A test shot.
This is nice.
Zhao Xilun's smile is so bright.
Yes.
You guys haven't checked
that out, have you?
(Wishing well)
That one.
The sign.
Oh yes.
I'll read it out for you all.
Yeah.
Let's check that out.
The coin guide.
Yeah, we haven't figured out
the rules yet.
(Approaching)
Where's the button?
I think
here.
That looks like it.
(Wishing well. Stargazing room. City date)
Everyone gets three coins.
One unlocks it once.
Yes.
There's only one date per week.
Only one person can use the city date
(Gets closer)
each week.
So only one chance a week?
(Asks)
Yes.
Does that mean we can
start booking it today?
I don't know.
He already wants to make bookings.
Booking?
I am
going to guard
the entrance today.
I'll see who comes down.
I stayed up for two days
to wait for today.
(Laughs)
Once everyone's asleep,
I'll go down to eat
and put in the coin.
When you
come down at 3AM,
you'll see me sitting there.
(Laughs)
(Asks)
Was this just put here today?
Since yesterday.
I saw this
when I came in.
I have sharp eyes.
When I entered with my luggage,
I saw it immediately.
I read through it already.
What if one person
uses all three coins?
You can.
But don't use them all at once.
You only get
a city date once a week.
Two people using all six coins.
And...
Keep going on dates.
They have the whole month booked.
(Laughs)
(Glances)
(Walks away)
(Takes a photo at the same time)
A sneak photo.
Sneak photo
of the person sneaking a photo.
I already gave you
a close-up.
Let me see.
I can't see it.
Sneaky vibes.
Perfect.
You're amazing.
We can see it from here
actually.
So we have to toss the coin
into that?
Then...
Then press either this button
or that one there.
So this is the button,
right?
Yes.
If it were you,
which would you pick?
(Asks)
Which one do you like?
Yakitori or steak,
right?
Either is fine.
Foie gras.
Which one do you like?
Adults don't make choices.
I like them all.
(Laughs from his joke)
How do you
feel about rides
in amusement parks?
I like them.
Do you?
You're not afraid?
(Glances)
I can ride the drop tower.
Can you?
You'd even ride that?
I think it's alright.
You're pretty brave.
Are they leaving?
Yeah.
Let's go together.
It's so pretty in here too.
But we didn't find that shuttlecock.
The shuttlecock.
Well.
Come in.
(This way)
Okay.
Why are you...
Please come in.
Hello, welcome.
Thank you.
Have you been
to this space?
No.
It's my first time
in here.
The rock climbing.
Yeah.
Popcorn.
Is it a machine?
Or what?
Jasmine tea.
Amazing.
It is indeed popcorn.
Cool.
Your sight
is spot on.
Stuff you saw today.
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to play badminton.
Here's the racket.
But no shuttlecock.
Use this.
(Joking)
Hit that?
(Looks)
(Looking for shuttlecock)
Found it.
Where?
He found it.
You both
didn't even find it.
We didn't.
Anyone?
Me.
For you.
(Passes to her)
Thank you.
They're playing in here.
Where did the shuttlecock go?
Chen Hewen, can you teach me
how to play?
Sure.
Who will join me?
It shall be you.
(Invites)
Play here? Really?
Yeah. Just play.
It's fine. Exercise after dinner.
I think we should
play outside.
Let's go.
For real?
Yes.
Let's play.
(Change venue)
Playing because we're in the mood.
A little exercise after dinner.
But the wind feels strong.
(Watching)
(Follows)
You're pretty good at this.
I'm sorry.
I suck.
I'll be the judge.
You will?
One point.
Isn't that a lost?
You!
No.
This is the boundary line
where I'm standing.
Pass the line,
and you get a point.
You try too.
It went over.
Where's the net?
(Laughing)
I'll stand in the middle then.
In the middle?
It's a little dangerous.
(Offer to be the net)
I'll just hit the net.
I might hit you.
Hang on.
I'm a little scared
to be honest.
This is scary.
Honestly.
Hit him.
(Laughs)
One more.
There's also..
Why is there a line?
And a...
They're playing outside.
(Go out together)
Let's...
Let us...
We'll stand in a row.
We can stand in a row.
In a row.
This is so fun.
It's dangerous.
Because Sha Yue'er
hits the shuttle cock straight down.
Goes there.
Must we do this?
Quite powerful.
You must've eaten well today.
Just now.
(Laughing from his joke)
Good.
That hit was good.
Nice.
Two talented players.
(Praises)
I'm so bad.
It's fine.
Not at all.
(Choose to quit)
Who wants to play?
(Waves)
You guys play.
Let me.
Here.
You're not playing?
Yeah. You play.
Your whole body
should be around this position.
Around...
I can't really say what angle it is,
But try to hit it at the highest point.
Okay.
Reach for it.
Go easy on me, okay?
Go easy on me.
You go easy on me.
I'll start.
So high up.
(Laughs)
I told you to go easy on me.
Does this mean you want me
to catch it?
I will...
It's for you.
For the judge.
Let me pass first.
Looks like your skills
are better than mine.
No.
(Hits the roof)
You really like that roof, huh?
Anyone want to play?
Here.
I'll take a break.
It's just exercise anyway.
Let's play.
The two of you.
Take a break.
A master.
A hidden expert.
Me?
You call that a hidden expert?
You must've practiced your swing.
You've all learned.
You even know backhand shots.
You can play backhand?
I used to play,
but it's been too long since I played.
I only know how to do this.
Me too.
I only know this.
But your drop shots are accurate.
(Praise)
If you hadn't learned,
you wouldn't
be able to drop it
so steadily.
Drop what?
You have a good sense of space.
The space is only so big,
but you can get it over.
(Looks)
You can tell they're professional.
Yes.
(Trips)
Careful.
He went out.
You want me
to fall into the river,
huh?
♪Morning steam rises
from breakfast stalls♪
♪Packed subway cars,
barely room to breathe♪
♪Still half asleep, another day begins♪
♪The city glows beneath the towers♪
♪Somewhere beyond the clouds,
a sweet little date awaits♪
♪But first,
there are endless meetings to survive♪
♪Even if the fairy tale
only lasts a day♪
♪I'll still give it everything I have♪
♪Love out loud♪
♪Don't let this summer slip away♪
♪Cupid's arrow is already on its way♪
♪Don't act like you didn't see it♪
♪Just be a little braver♪
♪Keep moving♪
♪There's a little spark shining
in your eyes♪
♪That's the signal
of a heart coming alive♪
♪Keep moving♪
♪Life can be complicated,
yet beautifully simple♪
♪Go discover♪
♪That heartbeat you've been longing
to let out♪
♪Come closer♪
♪There's a little spark shining
in your eyes♪
♪That's the signal
of a heart coming alive♪